

DARIA SHATILO

SENIOR MONETIZATION AND SYSTEMS DESIGNER

CONTACT INFORMATION

T: +34-681-399-773 E-mail: dshatilo@gmail.com Linkedin: https://bit.ly/3rKoE9i Tableau portfolio: https://tabsoft.co/3pcPlBy

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a professional Monetization and Systems Designer with over 6 years of experience in game design, live-ops, and data analysis. Shipped several titles across different genres: Tycoon, City-Builder, Racing, Runner, Shooter. Have experience dealing with IPs: Disney, Universal (Despicable Me), Hasbro (My Little Pony)

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Motivated, well-disciplined and fast learning individual
- Find joy in assisting others
- Team player
- Languages: Russian (native), English (Advanced), Spanish (basic)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Excel** economy balancing and simulation
- **Machinations** crafting game systems, simulation, economy balancing in an interactive way
- Tableau data analysis and visualization
- **Economy modeling** a holistic vision of all game systems based on the design premises and expected behavior of a player
- **Forecasting** KPIs projections for a game in production or new feature (Revenues, Downloads, ARPI)

PROJECTS

- My Little Pony
- Little Big City 2
- Gangstar 4
- Despicable Me: Minion Rush
- Asphalt 9
- Unannounced RPG

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Monetization and Systems Designer OMNIDRONE Omnidrone (January 2020 - Present)

- KPIs estimations for a to-be-released game that is currently in production
- Economy modeling based on assumptions of player expected behavior and economy premises, identifying potential "pinch-points" and their points of exposure
- Systems design and economy balancing
- Competitors Systems, Roadmap, LTV Analysis, and Events Teardowns

Game Economy Designer



Gameloft (2015 - 2020)

- Balancing the needs for mobile games, their relation, life cycle
- Identifying the potential sale drivers for the different product categories in the game economy, defining the key points of exposure for those drivers
- Progression estimation and design
- Design of the test required to contrast the theory with Playtesting team
- Manage the behavioral economy included in the game
- Optimize the economic model in the game

Financial Analyst



Anheuser-Busch InBev (2012 - 2015)

Project "Standardization of invoicing in Ukraine and Russia" (This project took 1st place in the "Company Talents")

- Accounting and analyzing opportunities to minimize the number of parked documents in the future, reducing the number of goods received over 3 months
- Continuous interaction with the accountants and initiators for timely made payments to our suppliers and to maintain their loyalty to the company Project "Optimization of the business-processes in the PTP (Procurement to Pay) department"
- Optimization of the existed processes to eliminate non-value adding steps
- Measure potential benefits and present a Cost-Benefit Analysis to the Top Management.

EDUCATION

National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute"

Master's Degree "International Business and Finance", Diploma with honours (2007- 2013)

COURSES:

1C 8.2 "Enterprise" - CRM and accounting

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

- Reading books on Behavioral Economics
- Playing mobile games
- Walking on the beach